>> Brian Holt: 我们先把它放在 details.js上。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
let's go put it in details.js.
>> Brian Holt: 那么详细信息是什么?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So details is what?
一个班，所以我不能用这里的钩子，太不好玩了。
A class, so I can't use any hooks in here,
which is unfun.
所以我们要在这里说
So what we're gonna do
here is we're gonna say
从 ./ThemeContext 导入 ThemeContext 。
import ThemeContext from./ThemeContext.
>> Brian Holt: 不幸的是，使用类的上下文是非常奇怪的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And unfortunately, it's
a lot weirder to use context with classes.
所以我要在这个按钮上做什么
So, what I'm gonna do
here where the button is,
我们得去做特美康特
we have to do ThemeContext.Consumer.
>> 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 然后在这个过程中，你提供了一个功能。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then inside of this,
you're provided a function.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，在这里，我在这里得到一个主题的功能。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So inside of this,
I get a function here with the theme back.
然后我可以用这个主题来，我可以从这个主题中读出来。
And then here I can use this theme to,
I can read from the theme.
所以让我们把神虎克
So let's put themeHook.
> > Brian Holt: 接下来，我可以把我的按钮移到这里。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then here I can
just move my button up into this.
>> Brian Holt: 我可以说 style=backgroundColour
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
I can say style=backgroundColour
themeHook(0)，对吧 ?
themeHook(0), right?
因为它既为您提供了设置，也提供了主题和设置主题。
Because it provides you both the set,
or the theme and the set theme.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So keep in mind,
任何仅返回标记的函数都是 React 组件，对吗 ?
any function that just returns
markup is a React component, right?
所以我们只是在做一个小雷法元件
So we're just basically creating
a smaller React component inside of
主题提供程序。
the theme provider.
或者对正在从上下文中读取的主题使用者表示遗憾。
Or sorry the theme consumer,
which is reading that off of the context.
所以它是一种奇怪的模式，但它是这样运作的。
So it's kind of an odd pattern,
but that's how it works.
有道理吗
Does that make sense?
现在，读这个神钩(0) 是很奇怪的。
Now, it's weird to read this
themeHook(0) like this.
如果我们这样做的话我们可以让这更简单
So we could actually make this
even simpler if we just did this,
那么， >> Brian Holt: 我在这里做了什么 ?
so,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So what did I do here?
我毁了这个权利
I destructured this right.
现在我把主题从数组中拉出来。
Now I'm pulling the theme
out of the array.
> > Brian Holt: 但你可以把它留给神虎克 (0)，我很好。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But you could leave it with
the themeHook(0), I'm fine with that.
>> Brian Holt: 有意义吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Make sense?
>> Brian Holt: 因此，如果我们现在在这里，请转至详细信息页面。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So if we go over
here now to the details page.
>> Brian Holt: 请注意，他们现在已在不同页面上，但
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So notice that
they're on different pages now but
他们都是深蓝色背景他们都是从语境中读出来的
they're both dark blue backgrounds right
and they're both reading from context.
>> Brian Holt: 如果您更改该值。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And if you go change that.
所以如果我进入 app.js 并说
So if I go into the app.js and say.
是啊这不应该是深蓝色的
Yeah, this shouldn't be dark blue anymore,
这应该是 peru，是我最喜欢的 CSS 名称。
this should be peru,
it's my favorite CSS name color.
那是秘鲁的颜色
That's the color of Peru.
我不知道你是否知道但这就是它的原因
I don't know if you knew that but
that's what it is.
>> Brian Holt: 但通知会更新整个应用程序。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But
notice it updates the entire application.
>> Brian Holt: 有意义吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Make sense?
是吗马克
Yeah, Mark?
>> 演讲者 2: 我们能否将多个挂钩传递到上下文中 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Could we pass
multiple hooks to the context?
>> Brian Holt: 在那个时候
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: At that point,
你不会想用 > > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特
you wouldn't wanna use a
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You would just give it
一个对象，对吧 ?
an object, right?
你不会给它多钩子，你只会给它一个物体，对吧 ?
You wouldn't give it multiple hooks,
you would give it just an object, right?
所以，现在，这只是一个字符串。
So rather than here,
this is just a string right now.
我要做的大概就是说对象。
And probably what I would do
is I would just say object.
我就会有深蓝色的纽扣
And I would have buttonColor darkblue and
也许我不知道莫达色
maybe like, I don't know, modalColor.
莫达有颜色吗
Do modals have colors?
我不知道我不知道
I don't know.
它们是粉红色的，因为这是一个精心设计的应用。
And they're pink, because this
is a well-designed application.
好的，然后我就会有这个，所以我会在这里详细说明。
Okay, and then now I would have this and
so I would come into the details here.
那就是我的扣眼颜色对吧
And that would be theme.buttonColor,
right?
因此，您将使用对象，而不只是使用字符串。
So you would use an object
instead of just a string.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特:
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But again,
记住我什么都能给你用上下文对吧
just remember that I can give
anything to use context, right?
所以如果我回到 app.js， >> Brian Holt:
So if I go back to app.js,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Instead
我可以给它一个物体和一个物体
of having themeHook be a hook here,
I can actually just give it an object and
对象会有一堆东西对吧
that object would have a bunch
of stuff in it, right?
所以它不一定是钩子。
So it doesn't have to be a hook.
上下文中的挂钩不是 [LAUGH] 连接在一起，对吗 ?
Hooks in context are not
[LAUGH] hooked together, right?
它们是完全不同的概念。
They're totally separate concepts.
我碰巧在这里用他们在一起因为他们合作得很好
I happen to be using them here together
because they work together nicely.